[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular female musician appeared alongside Whoopi Goldberg in the 1993 comedy movie Sister Act 2: Back in the Habit?", "correct_answer": "Lauryn Hill", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary J. Blige", "Brandy", "Mariah Carey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1993 movie Angelina Jolie played her first ever leading role.", "correct_answer": "Cyborg 2", "incorrect_answers": ["Without Evidence", "Hackers", "Lookin to Get Out"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the Chinese meal called Char siu?", "correct_answer": "Pork", "incorrect_answers": ["Duck", "Fish", "Chicken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A serving of espresso contains more caffeine than a serving of instant coffee.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During a new moon phase, is the moon visible?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is said to be helpful in reducing swelling from bee stings?", "correct_answer": "Onion", "incorrect_answers": ["Pumpkin", "Pinto beans", "Parsley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This sign is ruled by Venus and people born under it are known as peacemakers.", "correct_answer": "Libra", "incorrect_answers": ["Pisces", "Capricorn", "Aquarius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the author of the musical theme of the movie?", "correct_answer": "Paul Anka", "incorrect_answers": ["Phillip Glass", "Maurice Jarre", "John Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to the fear of imperfection?", "correct_answer": "Atelophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ailurophobia", "Autophobia", "Arachnophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1932 movie Scarface: The Shame of the Nation was based on the life of this notorious gangster.", "correct_answer": "Al Capone", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Vito Corleone", "Clyde Barrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1997 film Face/Off, starring Nicolas Cage and John Travolta, was originally written for Arnold Schwarzenegger and Sylvester Stallone as a sci-fi movie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is NOT a species of dolphin?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["Orca", "Pilot whale", "False Killer Whale"]}]